

Austin Anderson

DevOps Engineer

Profile

Currently working as a DevOps Engineer with Automated Logic Corporation. I am a passionate and driven professional with experience in software development as well as Quality Assurance testing and automation.

I am responsible for managing and maintaining the build system as well as the CI/CD pipeline for numerous products in our R&D department. Experience working with Java, Python, Gradle,

Groovy and more to develop automation scripts, full-stack web development, and build systems.

Employment History

DevOps Engineer at Automated Logic Inc., Kennesaw

January 2018 - Present

- Responsible for managing build system with our R&D department using Gradle/Groovy/Java.
- Developing the CI/CD pipeline for multiple products using tools such as: TeamCity, Artifactory, Perforce, Rally, SonarQube.
- Responsible for maintaining legal integrity of thirdparty libraries using WhiteSource.
- System admin responsibilities for several internal tool servers, experience with both Windows and Linux environments.

Firmware Automation Intern at Automated Logic Inc., Kennesaw

January 2017 - January 2018

- Worked as firmware automation tester intern to develop and test Python automation scripts that leveraged API's to interact with firmware modules.
- Used Python and the Django Web framework to help develop full stack internal sites for testing and reporting purposes.

Details

Atlanta, GA, USA

470-955-5743

anderson81716@gmail.com

Links

Personal Website

Skills

- Full Stack Web Dev Using Django/Spring Boot Frameworks
- Automation Scripting
- Working with Virtual Environments for Dev/Deployment
- Using CI/CD Tools for Build Management
- Working in Agile/Scrum Development Environments
- 3rd-Party Library and License
- Compliance/Management
- Manual QA Testing
- Working with API's

• Developed several simple GUI tools using Python to assist in debugging and reporting firmware module logging.

Quality Assurance Intern at RTI Inc., Marietta

February 2015 – January 2017

- Participated in daily and weekly Scrum reporting.
- Used VBscript to write and run automation tests for desktop restaurant back office software application.
- Worked in Scrum and Agile work environments- manually testing enhancements and bug fixes.
- Worked with a team of software developers to plan, create, and test backlog items to be accomplished on several software products.

Education History

B.S. in Computer Science, Kennesaw State University, Kennesaw

August 2013 - July 2017